export const dataOfLesson1 = [
  {
    qid: "1",
    question: "Q-1. 4+5=?",
    answer: "9",
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "2",
    question: "Q-2. 4*6=?",
    answer: "24",
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "3",
    question: "Q-3. 4-7=?",

    answer: "-3",
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "4",
    question: "Q-4. 8/4=?",

    answer: "2",
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "5",
    question: "Q-5. 4*4+4=?",

    answer: "20",
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: "",
  },
];
export const dataOfLesson2 = [
  {
    qid: "1",
    question: "Capital Of USA ?",
    isVisited: false,
    answer: "Washington DC",
    Options: ["New York", "Washington DC", "Los Angeles"],
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "2",
    question: "Delhi is  the Capital of ?",

    answer: "India",
    Options: ["India", "France", "China"],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    answeredByStudent: "",
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "3",
    question: "Most Populated country in world",

    answer: "India",
    Options: ["China", "India", "USA"],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    answeredByStudent: "",
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "4",
    question: "zero was invented by which country",

    answer: "India",
    Options: ["China", "India", "USA"],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    answeredByStudent: "",
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "5",
    question: "Longest river in World",
    answer: "Nile",
    Options: ["Amazon River", "Nile", "Mississippi River"],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    answeredByStudent: "",

    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
];

export const dataOfLesson3 = [
  {
    qid: "1",
    question: "Select the numbers That is  divisible by 2",

    Options: ["2", "4", "5", "8", "6"],
    answer: ["2", "4", "6", "8"],

    optionsSelected: {
      "2": false,
      "4": false,
      "5": false,
      "8": false,
      "6": false,
    },

    answeredByStudent: [],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
  {
    qid: "2",
    question: "Select the numbers That is  divisible by 2",
    Options: ["2", "4", "5", "8", "6"],
    answer: ["2", "4", "6", "8"],
    optionsSelected: {
      "2": false,
      "4": false,
      "5": false,
      "8": false,
      "6": false,
    },
    answeredByStudent: [],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },

  // {
  //   qid: "3",
  //   question: "4+7=?",

  //   answer: "7",
  //   isVisited: false,
  //   isFlag: false,
  //   noOfAttempts: 7,
  //   natureOfAttempt: "",
  // },
  // {
  //   qid: "4",
  //   question: "4+8=?",

  //   answer: "7",
  //   isVisited: false,
  //   isFlag: false,
  //   noOfAttempts: 7,
  //   natureOfAttempt: "",
  // },
  // {
  //   qid: "5",
  //   question: "4+9=?",

  //   answer: "7",
  //   isVisited: false,
  //   isFlag: false,
  //   noOfAttempts: 7,
  //   natureOfAttempt: "",
  // },
];
export const dataOfLesson4 = [
  {
    qid: "1",
    question: "Sort All below options",
    Options: ["A", "B", "D", "C"],
    answer: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },

  {
    qid: "2",
    question: "Sort All below options",
    Options: ["10", "20", "40", "30"],

    answer: ["10", "20", "30", "40"],
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
];
export const dataOfLesson5 = [
  {
    qid: "1",
    question: "Match the options",

    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    fixedOptions: ["A", "B", "C"],
    answer: [],

    DragabbleOptions: [
      {
        img:
          "https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSLIy6J349mbu7PUEYc5MLJ-G22K1R_lkK2ow&usqp=CAU",
        type: "B",
      },
      {
        img:
          "data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAOEAAADhCAMAAAAJbSJIAAAAilBMVEX///8AAADd3d38/PzLy8v09PTl5eXT09OoqKj4+Pjv7+/y8vLs7OzFxcV/f3/Y2Ni0tLQfHx9gYGCurq6/v78hISGJiYm4uLhHR0eenp6VlZWCgoKNjY1wcHDOzs43NzdUVFQtLS1KSkoSEhKbm5tlZWURERFISEg+Pj5ra2tSUlIpKSkgICBAQEB5n1zFAAAJhElEQVR4nO2d6XqyOhCAiwqiVlxwqbvUtl+X0/u/vVNQFBVmJskkIX36/myFZAgks2Xy8PDHH+J0gnarP5nHcRjGw0m/NQia8jcLU1p8nVOhGbTj9ebbK2U6noXbQPym3ezqiL+3gnQa8ep7VC5bkdHzev4odOd5dt2rpn4T2a73uGwFks2QLuVHdsmTxu4jNBYVbyXCYbYlfZv+8edT3XKU09xGhBezWshNHxcyPv3YgDh3tKM3BfGOvEVtpJWdLQmDF2XpTowWXaCdSf4zY5IdaY255MvYDCpbmua/gR4DO+EO6q4UT5Pypi5vSsOYeP6SXbyMQ1zS2ODyf+x75aK3pvf5bZq8//vc7/fPT7tkiv9+FN7OrN3D5b99MwISx+9pteg3Av/62QSNycvqHbzuEF5fUnwsFa8xLwuKcNEE1j2DyeoZuH55UXaGV/8oe4mZ6aMv2mgz9/H7/OBPAE1hPO81m53H+GY6W2oW7yFANc+IpoXltFfAo0ru/7bSJdmRJjbBjOcSd+2LrKobdqGKtL7g1iMJsy/jERjIG7SaTxHc9ktP4d4+ZfpK2TMJU8IW1q+XCv6JjCZtCfpmEaYMuP2INnnC9DYECb9Un2QFPrR2ed9cymIb+dBTOkxtXdMC2+RchHFjTIuEYLOvvPZMAzNYOL6HWz6gBkP8ekGQKVt2RaqmBz3UhL+9gj1fCrv5FEA+prGeiS2AFiZu42IAtKVPR/QBz+SQt6k+JCD/J3ihWlXlbRX8IvRaaq9VzS44WwFHUMaKEKFqFGeMbYAjqFvAylFkNJ+sfYM5T6Ut79nuD86inK9KJZ1SLZXNuGhAAn5wtQLzWNb2junmXWjR5WoEZVvS+BfTvRNoCMWCtyqU6PwHHuMC9A0ZcjtXdYTl+c4gAY3MMjn+4a59DmUfXAi5vgMi98Y3g0MhgAQ0GN46cmcuVgcZqTQTSEDtXvW77txGEdSnAdDjlTD0WZBb3UrZfBqWSsb3iohz40VRNS56oIB6owYV+Nd9UP1O4NiS0TyBM9frvuJqFYICvvD0WJiryUYtea9U1z0z0uRRR5kXezFWutUnKKEJo7CcokdTSe+H59E3rv6K02fqRudeCSzC7McTojiICrcBFW5vxNZdCYqDKH8X0Ky3+RWmFAZRfr5D0iz0BO6oFOwdaQOxzGVQYM3ZXwkubilpzREJ3NlRZy5cdJGt5B3mgHSe9ST5Hyvq3BVZ8ymBJbS/leNsCku622NIPOO+izLOU73kpA4LaE3nLpJ7+eXmPOQr1BA9FyfXKeWMiwQW8Jm5s1Lkc41UTAFODrCtz+ScPEhS5hOY8uSZ9ONDnHSST4lL24iA7+ydlePYGxkDEcwJ8phj5wocE3glXA0+IqBxP3cVp6ituA2ApcvVYLk/kWT9EU9tSxAJ7W9NzTm+psJGAGI2GdrFQWIg99Ggqbk6Eh4lyaxEUSsAnWf+aemrHJmBIWpcYCqp7k0cQnQefxCdS9FdMCbj9jpoYgJa91+ogr6kVrZPc1KZ5phjJWbISAcdwroopbLAWylSTO281QW+a6wetqE8CSZgfdRuOeDsoBQZi7pOwDHRFOMpQswgW3A8u3FRDlABXZ9K4fygjBqZTjKA+fgZB1sZJkzg5S1q4e1WAN8JbygtXxdNvLyT0ZxnfrqogDWJWEiDTzSuG/hwJmKG48shYYu/45YFXOonw3YXFSFUbbLdRTXgfNkMixmXHCCpein6SokYgbBYqKUcW4ewWNQnsCYFoeaN40oboTqT4z4MQo0tx93BhAXfccUbTs3PcNwPhQvoumlBkNB+4qwSBAndNp7wwFp9sqHkICjejkuIR2X+JKw7BOPpT8Ka8/sl/P3f4e+X8Pevh4SoheMS4jl7ruulf7ZFSn1SvKUgSGigUL9OCGELx/00cBWMDMe9iXhClPU96ooQjlJx3KtPOKvJ8cgMnsRuo7YXJ2CJ0hO2+6gGxbiw3Uc1fMKRcI7nYiS4hI6r3oTwmuOBC0IQ2PEAIp7H7vqeIIK3bW+7j2oQYjNTx7Ogy8ueX+F4JjvBupCtylQTCFON41Y+QTN13H4iuGqMlZjXBEGrUTkwrgYQjqyzURyZEcKa77je9oDvKXF81wxaXshz3QhGq3x5rsef8Momzvu98cIfrnsUsZKQKXarzypDeE0dDyIS4jOuq6a4fWG1zjUDhNfUcZciYY9enSpFyYDVhfScV2uwOtee+7Mpvv/Jde2bYOk7bgYjhyKkuG4k4oFE1ysNEazEOsWgVhI18vBBfOLvqCwzqe1YaF26+tjBWbnVvXBsGh/EuliJeVas8IXODOLJFBJPR8MH0foJFxmnPC6Z0kd4GKoOFkZeBFEm7xXP+q5B9YE8+X4vdTXu4LefMJzvXJbM8kETaq3X/coVE9msV7zQp+Vs09wGkk8nrPmKca6sLj/l4R4bm8mY5/VMxaeCJ5zay/tu/pf3Qek2uO/UWrz0HH1Q86jglSKZjjYX5uwQVPX74cE2Oxr4OelePXECd57aONzq4pdnOHgKD3ubV20ubxZHLJOQu2B6trmoIjz2DSGgaPYsgUvi1ohpmsPtqINJEQuZaWynv32jIn6Zy8ksCMhXDohQP5nrfUEpTAucETDCVpM3MxsxCucY8S7EuCHlvZmYUQtVARNm45RQjs9AyK1oCbC/M4SkRe3aTXH3oAbLlLDbxBtrdWsUFUgt2eaELHdvqs/o7xRPnZQ8IBcDjyp6+kziq8PgtNXFI+wT9rwnLcN4tYFXY+E/yreowwPXvfI1aN0PQVk0PPbP5Fr312ysEQrxpnwzxjQG11uVtK+6lN3QKWMmGbs3U7iBcJCPWxpHnhme9uONfFMz2i+hNv2R3VDN4mjctvRsyoIhWP05kfzaMbnLxzaY1xokdBlHSxkh2yVVmzUpMhUQykZfSNZbkder05r9V3IT01Eg9EjdG8aLLUktby/KN5dFFmKVQsOYMY1etkGVR6cZDOJVVd7nm50UrAaeh1pG8u9jGcbzfnvQ+KHd6g/DRbTfQZ7njbX9DwKTqgIjq/m6JHNDDduJnrdaBzdRDc7mDTTK+Mrm1VbD1/SubmoiX0onlptXIWZ1K/bTJivkFJK4lhvk5oS97hQOCvq6bnpDZSEPm5btZDIEvzXDA+NVfK1p2qt1epPoGRfnhvdoXoO1T4DOII6+iaO5G4ctV+veBIPhMvqsPN4lGc8W/YbrW4yOdFMroj+P4zCMh/NJv9X+JYL9oZP/AVxobhGHGSGGAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC",
        type: "C",
      },
      {
        img:
          "https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRinRa6Y-0gtOlzAkJ6Dh39YA3gCRuXOFC9ew&usqp=CAU",
        type: "A",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    qid: "1",
    question: "Match the options",

    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    fixedOptions: ["A", "B", "C"],
    answer: [],

    DragabbleOptions: [
      {
        img:
          "https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSLIy6J349mbu7PUEYc5MLJ-G22K1R_lkK2ow&usqp=CAU",
        type: "B",
      },
      {
        img:
          "data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAOEAAADhCAMAAAAJbSJIAAAAilBMVEX///8AAADd3d38/PzLy8v09PTl5eXT09OoqKj4+Pjv7+/y8vLs7OzFxcV/f3/Y2Ni0tLQfHx9gYGCurq6/v78hISGJiYm4uLhHR0eenp6VlZWCgoKNjY1wcHDOzs43NzdUVFQtLS1KSkoSEhKbm5tlZWURERFISEg+Pj5ra2tSUlIpKSkgICBAQEB5n1zFAAAJhElEQVR4nO2d6XqyOhCAiwqiVlxwqbvUtl+X0/u/vVNQFBVmJskkIX36/myFZAgks2Xy8PDHH+J0gnarP5nHcRjGw0m/NQia8jcLU1p8nVOhGbTj9ebbK2U6noXbQPym3ezqiL+3gnQa8ep7VC5bkdHzev4odOd5dt2rpn4T2a73uGwFks2QLuVHdsmTxu4jNBYVbyXCYbYlfZv+8edT3XKU09xGhBezWshNHxcyPv3YgDh3tKM3BfGOvEVtpJWdLQmDF2XpTowWXaCdSf4zY5IdaY255MvYDCpbmua/gR4DO+EO6q4UT5Pypi5vSsOYeP6SXbyMQ1zS2ODyf+x75aK3pvf5bZq8//vc7/fPT7tkiv9+FN7OrN3D5b99MwISx+9pteg3Av/62QSNycvqHbzuEF5fUnwsFa8xLwuKcNEE1j2DyeoZuH55UXaGV/8oe4mZ6aMv2mgz9/H7/OBPAE1hPO81m53H+GY6W2oW7yFANc+IpoXltFfAo0ru/7bSJdmRJjbBjOcSd+2LrKobdqGKtL7g1iMJsy/jERjIG7SaTxHc9ktP4d4+ZfpK2TMJU8IW1q+XCv6JjCZtCfpmEaYMuP2INnnC9DYECb9Un2QFPrR2ed9cymIb+dBTOkxtXdMC2+RchHFjTIuEYLOvvPZMAzNYOL6HWz6gBkP8ekGQKVt2RaqmBz3UhL+9gj1fCrv5FEA+prGeiS2AFiZu42IAtKVPR/QBz+SQt6k+JCD/J3ihWlXlbRX8IvRaaq9VzS44WwFHUMaKEKFqFGeMbYAjqFvAylFkNJ+sfYM5T6Ut79nuD86inK9KJZ1SLZXNuGhAAn5wtQLzWNb2junmXWjR5WoEZVvS+BfTvRNoCMWCtyqU6PwHHuMC9A0ZcjtXdYTl+c4gAY3MMjn+4a59DmUfXAi5vgMi98Y3g0MhgAQ0GN46cmcuVgcZqTQTSEDtXvW77txGEdSnAdDjlTD0WZBb3UrZfBqWSsb3iohz40VRNS56oIB6owYV+Nd9UP1O4NiS0TyBM9frvuJqFYICvvD0WJiryUYtea9U1z0z0uRRR5kXezFWutUnKKEJo7CcokdTSe+H59E3rv6K02fqRudeCSzC7McTojiICrcBFW5vxNZdCYqDKH8X0Ky3+RWmFAZRfr5D0iz0BO6oFOwdaQOxzGVQYM3ZXwkubilpzREJ3NlRZy5cdJGt5B3mgHSe9ST5Hyvq3BVZ8ymBJbS/leNsCku622NIPOO+izLOU73kpA4LaE3nLpJ7+eXmPOQr1BA9FyfXKeWMiwQW8Jm5s1Lkc41UTAFODrCtz+ScPEhS5hOY8uSZ9ONDnHSST4lL24iA7+ydlePYGxkDEcwJ8phj5wocE3glXA0+IqBxP3cVp6ituA2ApcvVYLk/kWT9EU9tSxAJ7W9NzTm+psJGAGI2GdrFQWIg99Ggqbk6Eh4lyaxEUSsAnWf+aemrHJmBIWpcYCqp7k0cQnQefxCdS9FdMCbj9jpoYgJa91+ogr6kVrZPc1KZ5phjJWbISAcdwroopbLAWylSTO281QW+a6wetqE8CSZgfdRuOeDsoBQZi7pOwDHRFOMpQswgW3A8u3FRDlABXZ9K4fygjBqZTjKA+fgZB1sZJkzg5S1q4e1WAN8JbygtXxdNvLyT0ZxnfrqogDWJWEiDTzSuG/hwJmKG48shYYu/45YFXOonw3YXFSFUbbLdRTXgfNkMixmXHCCpein6SokYgbBYqKUcW4ewWNQnsCYFoeaN40oboTqT4z4MQo0tx93BhAXfccUbTs3PcNwPhQvoumlBkNB+4qwSBAndNp7wwFp9sqHkICjejkuIR2X+JKw7BOPpT8Ka8/sl/P3f4e+X8Pevh4SoheMS4jl7ruulf7ZFSn1SvKUgSGigUL9OCGELx/00cBWMDMe9iXhClPU96ooQjlJx3KtPOKvJ8cgMnsRuo7YXJ2CJ0hO2+6gGxbiw3Uc1fMKRcI7nYiS4hI6r3oTwmuOBC0IQ2PEAIp7H7vqeIIK3bW+7j2oQYjNTx7Ogy8ueX+F4JjvBupCtylQTCFON41Y+QTN13H4iuGqMlZjXBEGrUTkwrgYQjqyzURyZEcKa77je9oDvKXF81wxaXshz3QhGq3x5rsef8Momzvu98cIfrnsUsZKQKXarzypDeE0dDyIS4jOuq6a4fWG1zjUDhNfUcZciYY9enSpFyYDVhfScV2uwOtee+7Mpvv/Jde2bYOk7bgYjhyKkuG4k4oFE1ysNEazEOsWgVhI18vBBfOLvqCwzqe1YaF26+tjBWbnVvXBsGh/EuliJeVas8IXODOLJFBJPR8MH0foJFxmnPC6Z0kd4GKoOFkZeBFEm7xXP+q5B9YE8+X4vdTXu4LefMJzvXJbM8kETaq3X/coVE9msV7zQp+Vs09wGkk8nrPmKca6sLj/l4R4bm8mY5/VMxaeCJ5zay/tu/pf3Qek2uO/UWrz0HH1Q86jglSKZjjYX5uwQVPX74cE2Oxr4OelePXECd57aONzq4pdnOHgKD3ubV20ubxZHLJOQu2B6trmoIjz2DSGgaPYsgUvi1ohpmsPtqINJEQuZaWynv32jIn6Zy8ksCMhXDohQP5nrfUEpTAucETDCVpM3MxsxCucY8S7EuCHlvZmYUQtVARNm45RQjs9AyK1oCbC/M4SkRe3aTXH3oAbLlLDbxBtrdWsUFUgt2eaELHdvqs/o7xRPnZQ8IBcDjyp6+kziq8PgtNXFI+wT9rwnLcN4tYFXY+E/yreowwPXvfI1aN0PQVk0PPbP5Fr312ysEQrxpnwzxjQG11uVtK+6lN3QKWMmGbs3U7iBcJCPWxpHnhme9uONfFMz2i+hNv2R3VDN4mjctvRsyoIhWP05kfzaMbnLxzaY1xokdBlHSxkh2yVVmzUpMhUQykZfSNZbkder05r9V3IT01Eg9EjdG8aLLUktby/KN5dFFmKVQsOYMY1etkGVR6cZDOJVVd7nm50UrAaeh1pG8u9jGcbzfnvQ+KHd6g/DRbTfQZ7njbX9DwKTqgIjq/m6JHNDDduJnrdaBzdRDc7mDTTK+Mrm1VbD1/SubmoiX0onlptXIWZ1K/bTJivkFJK4lhvk5oS97hQOCvq6bnpDZSEPm5btZDIEvzXDA+NVfK1p2qt1epPoGRfnhvdoXoO1T4DOII6+iaO5G4ctV+veBIPhMvqsPN4lGc8W/YbrW4yOdFMroj+P4zCMh/NJv9X+JYL9oZP/AVxobhGHGSGGAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC",
        type: "C",
      },
      {
        img:
          "https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRinRa6Y-0gtOlzAkJ6Dh39YA3gCRuXOFC9ew&usqp=CAU",
        type: "A",
      },
    ],
  },
];
export const dataOfLesson6 = [
  {
    qid: "1",
    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
    answeredByStudent: [],

    question: "Fill in the Blank",
    sentance: "I  _  to  *  Cricket $",
    Options: ["like", "alot", "watch"],
    answer: ["like", "watch", "alot"],
    wordsOrder: { like: "", watch: "", alot: "" },
  },
  {
    qid: "2",
    question: "Fill in the Blank",
    sentance: "I _ to * Cricket $",
    Options: ["like", "alot", "watch"],
    answeredByStudent: [],
    answer: ["like", "watch", "alot"],
    wordsOrder: { like: "", watch: "", alot: "" },

    isVisited: false,
    isFlag: false,
    noOfAttempts: 7,
    natureOfAttempt: "",
  },
];
